Since
we're talking about the third level of the
kingdom, the form,
what are we going to do, the third, the third
level of the kingdom, the form of four
days by Hans Sachs and Nîmes, these four
have sexy names, this by Harvard in
Game, these four have
boring names, Transformer, and the first, the
level of the form is made up of the
second level,
Robert Ford, fourth, infinite space,
infinite space, internet,
canches, nes, is infinite consciousness,
blindness, nothing at all, in which the
summit,
Webber, we will get to that,
so the third level of the form,
Falcones, has five components,
F
is the main difference between
level 2 and level 3, the ball to your
insides, fin, in level 2 you are inside
the thing, in the light star party in
Maine, and there your body and mind are
in ecstasy, sol, you must, Pichincha, can,
sicken, the difference between the second and
the third, and art 5 of Part 5 of
Gateway, okay, you have to think about the
person who gets drunk, oh, I would
n't have arrived, anti-football, manches,
watching live, I know that nobody here
has  Never drunk but
others have seen him get drunk on First Air
Selena first they're going crazy in the
East Kit drinking and yes yes they keep drinking
dislike
LAN Airlines and his heartbeat /
like before
parade for common line on the plateau if
that moment feeling the sense the
mental feeling
happy goes from happy
to unconscious
and that's the difference between 2 and 3 is the
inhabitant as if you've taken a
very strong drug
sleeping lecturer or like five
sleeping pills First Bank your
heart and the first you're happy in art
fire line and after five you're like this already
the mind at last in the
mental feeling is night
whoever it is I can't I can't
describe it in
words they just have to feel it like this the
flat plateau of Bari faithful in the
body feeling this Dutchman
if being like you're doing
a good yoga pose the body very
integrated
church
the body feels super charged like
a ballet dancer so when your
balance is perfect everything is super
charged
if the whole body you have knee problems
Chester crisis thong or you went to a
very strong ashtanga class
which makes you wish you could sit
in a chair on Friday deliver
Your knees interrupt your meditation. You
should sit in a chair. By
Jaime, nor defend meditations.
Washington EFE. Don't make this law
the express and the exception 'breaks'. I
try different postures, objects to
meditate and sit with, and because I know
someone who sits on bricks.
Only Nihat Burley, Wire in the Park, and
Uruguay in the body. You are like this,
all activated in mind. The feeling, the
mental feeling. We'll be a man.
While yesterday the mental feeling
went beyond mental pleasure to an
indescribable plateau in the great and tex.
Well, art to have, and maybe it will take you an
hour. It will arrive and surely disconnect from
here. So let's just pretend that we
must do to
sow a seed so that it
happens in the future
in the same way that we did when
trying to imagine our past life.
The first couple wish the fighter Ma
Ying-jeou. The first two weeks that
you try to imagine your past life and Google
are Fanny Stories Live from Fantastic.
Quite a video format and give so that
some funny stories will appear, like
the movie Fantastic Four, the
Fantastic Four in the live stream and
San Miguel.  rock can eat better and not
Santiago cam and how to see you said
suddenly you connect with a
real memory something real will appear software
form so let's try to
be on the third level of the kingdom of
form and Manning of Jordi and reading the
mere fact of imagining that you are
doing it here on YouTube and that can
cause you to be there
are distant in the bar and Fidel Suárez
the body is completely activated
modified mind film institute
and the mental feeling went from a
pleasant state to
dissolution the whistle hearts and mine
the mind if you are completely
awake nor punctual focused the fear
fix and two more things work in session
in Zinc
are very strong at this point in this
part you can tell me what session who
can tell me what turns and Zinc
is theme I
am without scamming to dance that if you have
the fire alarm
Jason this smart fit actor is the
smoke detector
and when it detects smoke
the alarm is activated I am Jaycee immense
state vacation alarm main 7 is an
alarm in the back of your mind
and nothing irsap basteri folketing Jaime
inside the heart flat line
se  It explains that your object of meditation is
inside the heart on a plateau, the x5
Javier Fort Koffice, but if you
suddenly think of our four coffees,
distracting the voice,
JR Firewall and Peep, and if
a thought of the four coffees suddenly arises, your
fire alarm goes off, Tit It
and Piti the News Chamba World Mba ya, and at
that moment you use Gemba, which is solitude,
after the mind, or the tension, or the focus
back to that plateau. My father and
fishing. My dad really liked to
fish.
During World War II, he was
on a submarine, San Gil, and they heard her, and she really
liked the sea, Anipac
Weaver,
and for you, that
animal and stupid people
in the attack on Los Pinos, where he
offered,
he bought a boat like a 20-
meter boat capable of firing torpedoes.
Other boats of that type, John F. Kennedy
was captain of this type of military boat. It's like
almost a suicide mission,
and it took us 34 days at
sea. Once, poker on face, and we played
poker and fish,
and the two fish they caught
were big.  like a tuna
and wait for English you have a
special belt with a big hole right
below your important place
the witness arrives
because I'm talking about this, about that
mango wei topic about the mind goes
and then brings it back you release the
reel and then you tighten it, you release it and
tighten it and it scales
alak yes if not you don't test them all
because that terrain
of speaking
you tighten the piece, you test the wings
but then you relax and let it go and then you
pull it if you let it go and that's how you move
and then my dad made us open the tuna
and take out the entrails there will be Capi and
Klein and you start in the place peeping the
character and you cut up to the
silver neck of the gentleman and you take out the guts from the
water city news leader and 15 years later
the doctor told him that he had a
heart problem
we have to do surgery on him
but don't worry and that he has the family home
we can grab a vein from your leg
in my mouth juniors be the place at
figure and we're going to cut you the same  that
since they cut the dog
I didn't know about karma but I thought I
missed you,
sorber survived but it was unpleasant, it will be
the third labor so at the
third level,
Fidel meta feeling, the mental feeling, they have, it seems they are
sleepy, they want to
do something, you
plan since the inguat trusts
you, your mind function, sastrón and there
are two mental functions that are already
strong,
the distraction detector alarm,
orangel Washington
maingot companies that is always
vigilant to see if the mind is
distracted to another place, if it
leaves your meditative object
which is the pleasure of the heartbeat,
and I always say if it is another extra place,
Colin and see, it brings it back, the
sporting opposes in a punctual way, it is like that, you have to
see and be one way to
die, Sting
Ribéry, Cleaver of the neutral, everyone
knows what neutral is,
Atlantean emission and ours made the
Spanish keys like tiger in the last
state, this is sugar of its own, the one that
lasts, you already drunk,
here the emotions enter us, they don't
move, my car and the good guys
and no  Knowing IGTM online,
they were drinking tea.
American Airlines
is talking about some people from China
who have special powers that
hit them and leave them immobile,
and there isn't much, there isn't much without the
mental state, it's like immutable, without
emotion, without a vial of image because
beyond any feeling that next month